<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tour FC</string>
    <string name="show_all">show all ></string>
    <string name="horsetooth_mountain_title">Horsetooth Mountain Park</string>
    <string name="mountain_whitewater_title">Mountain Whitewater Descents</string>
    <string name="flower_trial_garden_title">Annual Flower Trial Garden</string>
    <string name="horsetooth_reservoir_title">Horsetooth Reservoir</string>
    <string name="city_park_title">City Park</string>
    <string name="melting_pot_title">The Melting Pot</string>
    <string name="maza_kabob_title">Maza Kabob</string>
    <string name="rio_grande_title">Rio Grande</string>
    <string name="star_of_india_title">Star of India</string>
    <string name="lucile_title">Lucile\'s</string>
    <string name="cafe_athens_title">Cafe Athens</string>
    <string name="cafe_de_bangkok_title">Cafe de Bangkok</string>
    <string name="new_belgium_title">New Belgium Brewing Company</string>
    <string name="odell_brewing_title">Odell Brewing Company</string>
    <string name="anheuser_busch_title">Anheuser Busch Brewery</string>
    <string name="coopersmith_title">Coopersmith Pub and Brewing</string>
    <string name="social_title">Social</string>
    <string name="mayor_old_town_title">Mayor of Old Town</string>
    <string name="colorado_room_title">The Colorado Room</string>
    <string name="ace_gilletts_title">Ace Gilletts</string>
    <string name="elliots_martini_title">Elliot\'s Martini bar</string>
    <string name="top_activities">Top Activities</string>
    <string name="scenic_open_space">Scenic Open Space</string>
    <string name="white_water_rafting">White-water rafting</string>
    <string name="horticulture_display">Vibrant Horticulture display</string>
    <string name="top_restaurants">Top Restaurants</string>
    <string name="amazing_fondue">Amazing Fondue place</string>
    <string name="afghan_specialty">Afghan Specialties</string>
    <string name="indian_buffet">Best Indian Buffet</string>
    <string name="breakfast_place">Fantastic Breakfast Place</string>
    <string name="greek_mediterranean">Good Old Greek-Mediterranean</string>
    <string name="traditional_thai">Traditional Thai</string>
    <string name="best_outdoors">All-in-one Outdoors</string>
    <string name="ideal_relaxing_spot">Ideal Relaxing Spot</string>
    <string name="top_breweries">Top Breweries</string>
    <string name="new_belgium_free_tours">Great Free Tours</string>
    <string name="odell_microbrew">Decent Draft Microbrews</string>
    <string name="grand_tour">Magnificent Brewing House</string>
    <string name="top_bars_nightlife">Top Bars/Nightlife</string>
    <string name="amazing_margarita">Amazing Margaritas</string>
    <string name="creative_cocktails">Creative Cocktails</string>
    <string name="mayor_great_selction">Great Selection of Beers</string>
    <string name="colorado_beers_and_spirits">Good Craft Beers and Local Spirits</string>
    <string name="gilletts_crafted_beers">Superbly Crafted Cocktails</string>
    <string name="coopersmith_mixed_desc">Interesting Choice of Beers and Great Location</string>
    <string name="elliot_martini_variety">Large Selection of Martinis and Seasonal Cocktails</string>
    <string name="sample_detailed_description">Detailed description of the attraction</string>
    <string name="show_map">show in map</string>

    <string name="city_park_detailed_desc">
        City Park Pool is located in City Park.
        Enjoy the park surroundings and Sheldon Lake for fishing and an outdoor pool.
        City Park Pool is the best place to be during those hot summer days in Fort Collins.
        City Park Pool provides you with a water park experience right in your own backyard.
        Admission is charged for everyone entering City Park Pool.
    </string>

    <string name="horsetooth_reservoir_detailed_desc_card_text">
        Six and one-half miles of water beckon visitors to come out and play! Surrounded by
        1,900 acres of public lands, this reservoir has it all: fishing, boating, camping,
        picnicking, swimming, scuba diving, rock climbing, and water skiing.
    </string>

    <string name="flower_trail_garden_detailed_desc_card_text">
        The Annual Flower Trial Garden is a horticultural project at the Colorado State University
        in Fort Collins. Every year, the project sees new varietals of different flowers planted in
        the garden to assess their ability to develop and grow in the local climate, as well as
        their flowering characteristics. Open to public and free of charge.
    </string>

    <string name="horsetooth_mountain_park_detailed_desc_card_text">
        The scenic 2,711-acre Horsetooth Mountain Open Space (consisting of Culver, Soderberg,
        and Hughey Open Spaces) covers elevations from 5,430 to 7,255 feet. Its 29 miles of hiking,
        biking, and horseback riding trails connect to the Blue Sky Trail and Lory State Park trails.
        The outstanding Horsetooth Rock is a familiar local landmark visible from the plains.
    </string>

    <string name="mountain_whitewater_descents_detailed_desc_card_text">
        Mountain Whitewater Descents is a guide company offering whitewater rafting trips on
        Cache La Poudre River, equipment rentals and a pub. It prides itself on its special permit
        for using the river, which is the only "Wild and Scenic" river near Fort Collins and
        Estes Park, offering the best wilderness rafting experience.
    </string>

    <string name="the_melting_pot_detailed_desc_card_text">
        The only place in Fort Collins serving some amazing fondues, with the choice of heated pots
        of cheese, chocolate or broth for dipping and cooking. For the adventurous, local favorites
        also occupy a sizable portion of the menu. Waiters are friendly and helpful and they help
        you decide the food befitting your palate. Make reservations ahead of time.
    </string>

    <string name="maza_kabob_detailed_desc_card_text">
        Enjoy many delightful authentic Afghan recipes with savory flavors and mouth watering smells
        brought straight from the heart of Afghanistan. Locally owned and operated. Serving
        Fort Collins for more than 5 years!
    </string>

    <string name="rio_grande_detailed_desc_card_text">
        The "Start of it All" - Fort Collins is the original Rio. Located in the heart of Old Town,
        The Rio has become a popular destination for locals, students, and tourists to enjoy
        fresh Tex Mex and legendary margaritas.
    </string>

    <string name="star_of_india_detailed_desc_card_text">
        North Indian craft kitchen featuring local and international ingredients cooked fresh to
        order keeping you in mind! Dine in/take out. The owners of this fine establishment believe
        that spicy does not translate to "being hot". This is a go-to place for all indian food
        cravers and others who like to occasionally get a refreshing taste of indian flavors.
    </string>

    <string name="lucile_creole_detailed_desc_card_text">
        Amazing beignets, fantastic chicory coffee and other bayou-rific Cajun-Creole staples
        mark this area chain, where the rich and flavorful breakfast fare and awesome brunch
        are what fans expect when they go to heaven; the cozy, homey digs
        capture New Orleans, but get there early on weekends or prepare to bump elbows.
    </string>

    <string name="cafe_athens_detailed_desc_card_text">
        Delicious hot food, super fast service, awesome prices. Consistently on point every visit.
        Chicken, falafel, and souvlaki gyros are incredibly good for the price. Local favorite is
        the fries - double fried, nice and crispy, and perfectly salted. So good! Service is also
        pleasantly friendly for a busy greek restaurant.
    </string>

    <string name="cafe_de_bangkok_detailed_desc_card_text">
        Truly authentic Thai place in Ft Collins. If you are looking for fresh, authentic and
        traditional Thai food, this place is as good as you will find. Unbelievable flavor and
        spice that you won\'t find at most Thai or Asian cuisine restaurants. Chicken Cashew is a
        must try. You either will feel something entirely new or it may transport you back home.
    </string>

    <string name="new_belgium_detailed_desc_card_text">
        Free tour, getting to see behind the bottles of your favorite beer? Priceless. The tour
        is fun!! Completely different brewery tour experience. Its a little more than a hour tour
        with loads of new information about the process of beer brewing and get to learn all this in
        a fun way.
    </string>

    <string name="odell_brewing_detailed_desc_card_text">
        Odell breweries, is a gorgeous taproom just outside downtown Ft. Collins. There\'s ample
        space to sip and socialize both inside and out, as well as a great little section of
        souvenirs so tourists can bring back a memento of their visit. Bar service is friendly and
        efficient, and the there\'s a food counter along with a stage for local entertainment.
    </string>

    <string name="anheuser_busch_detailed_desc_card_text">
        The brewery tour is an immersive experience where you can hear, smell, touch and taste the
        components that go into some of the world’s most popular beers. Additionally, Fort Collins
        is the home to the world-famous Budweiser Clydesdales West Coast Team. You can get an
        up-close and personal encounter and have your picture taken with these iconic horses!
    </string>

    <string name="coopersmith_detailed_desc_card_text">
        Welcome to World-Famous CooperSmith\’s Pub and Brewing. Tucked into the heart of
        Old Town Fort Collins, CooperSmith\’s offers a distinct alternative in eating and drinking
        establishments. We invite you to enjoy our unique charm. Located across the walkway from
        CooperSmith\’s Pubside, Poolside offers not only additional brewery space but an upscale
        yet casual atmosphere.
    </string>

    <string name="social_detailed_desc_card_text">
        Social is a locally-owned, underground, cocktail bar in Old Town Fort Collins. It\'s a
        place to enjoy properly crafted cocktails, sommelier selected wines, and abundantly sliced
        charcuterie. At the entrance into Old Town Square, a street clock and a well-lit stairwell
        welcome you to an evening filled with great conversation. Friendly service and great
        quality food and beverage.
    </string>

    <string name="mayor_of_old_town_detailed_desc_card_text">
        Named one of the nation\'s top 100 beer bars, the Mayor of Old Town has 100 beers on tap
        and a passionate staff that\'ll help you find your ideal brew. Good food menu at a
        reasonable price, they really have a lot to choose from. This beer oasis is very close to
        Colorado State University campus and is in downtown Fort Collins area.
    </string>

    <string name="the_colorado_room_detailed_desc_card_text">
        Best place for Sliders and Poutine and Beer. It is right down the street from CSU, a
        nice patio out front and lot of Colorado memorabilia inside creates a funky place to
        hang out and get some good food and beer. Service is fantastic and friendly all around.
    </string>

    <string name="ace_gilletts_detailed_desc_card_text">
        Step away from one world and descend underground
        into another – a shadowy, smoldering enclave with walls nearly a century old that hold the
        memories and merriment of travelers and the surrounding neighborhood alike. Sip a
        handcrafted martini from our signature drink menu, or partake in that perfect pairing of
        wine and unforgettable fare.
    </string>

    <string name="elliot_martini_bar_detailed_desc_card_text">
        Cooking up inventive concoctions you could only dream of comes naturally to the talented
        bartenders at this marvelous Fort Collins martini bar that\'s both chic (huge windows
        and secluded booths) and chill (films projected on the wall); tabs are reasonable for what
        you\'re getting and the atmosphere\'s perfect for either a group outing or a date, keeping
        it a must-stop for many.
    </string>
    <string name="attraction_card_image_view_content_desc">ImageView displaying the attraction\'s image file</string>
    <string name="list_item_image_view_content_desc">Image of Attraction</string>
    <string name="list_item_right_arrow_image_content_desc">Right arrow image to move forward to the next activity</string>

</resources>
